-This is just a minor setback.
-No, it's not, okay?
I've been out here for,
like, ten years.
-I have nothing to show for it.
-Well, you have me.
I do have you.
Mmm.
Leonard Hofstadter,
will you marry me?
(Amy:)Um...
Did you seriously just say...umm?
(Sheldon:)-It's an outrage.
-I know.
(Sheldon:)The university, they think
they can do whatever they want.
(Sheldon:)We just have to sit
there and take it.
(Leonard:)You need to let it go, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)You work tirelessly for someone
and this is what you get.
Oh, my God! They're just making
you use your vacation days!
(Sheldon:)But I don't want a vacation.
(Leonard:)Okay, listen, I don't mean to
diminish what you're going through,
(Leonard:)but I'm a little
distracted right now.
(Sheldon:)Oh, this again?
(Sheldon:)So, Penny proposed,
you didn't say yes,